4anything.com 2002-11-25

# 4anything.com: Privacy Policy

**4anything.com Privacy Policy**

Please read the following to understand 4anything.com's views and practices regarding privacy and how they pertain to users of the 4anything.com Network.  
**  
4ANYTHING.COM PRIVACY POLICY  
**  
4anything.com, Inc. has developed this Privacy Policy for the benefit of the Users of its 4anything.com Network, to demonstrate its serious commitment to protecting privacy on the 4anything.com Network. Accordingly, the following information summarizes 4anything.com's personal data gathering and distribution practices for the 4anything.com Network as found at http://www.4anything.com.

As Internet technology changes, 4anything.com may change the content found on the 4anything.com Network, and consequently, its Privacy Policy. Please revisit our Privacy Policy from time to time to be sure that you are familiar with our current policy. Your continued use of the 4anything.com Network following any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be viewed as representing your acceptance of such changes. Please see 4anything.com's 

Terms & Conditions for more information on the terms and conditions governing the use of the 4anything.com Network.

**Why does 4anything.com need my personal information?** In order to provide our Users with a more personalized, relevant and intelligent service, 4anything.com regularly makes improvements to the 4anything.com Network. The collection of personal data greatly assists 4anything.com in this improvement process by identifying the specific interests and needs of the many Users of the 4anything.com Network. Data collection also assists 4anything.com by allowing it to advertise its products and/or services or the products and/or services of others in a more efficient manner.

Although 4anything.com's primary goal in collecting personal information is to deliver a customized and personalized service to Users, 4anything.com also uses the personal information it collects to send Users E-mail notifications of new features or information available through the 4anything.com Network, and other information that 4anything.com feels might be of interest to Users of the 4anything.com Network. 4anything.com also collects IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for system administration and troubleshooting purposes, and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and others. 4anything.com also collects and transfers to its appropriate partners the personal data volunteered by Users who request information or quotes for various services offered through the 4anything.com Network in order for such partners to provide the requested information or quotes. Lastly, 4anything.com uses personal information for verification purposes for the provision of some of its services, such as E-mail.

**How and what information does 4anything.com gather or track?** Through the use of "cookies" (as described below) and on-line data entry, survey and registration forms, 4anything.com may collect and/or monitor, in aggregate and individual form, personal identifying facts or data on, among other things, the following information:

**"Demographic" Information**

| 

**"Technical"  
Information**

| 

**"Reference" Information**  
  
---|---|---  
  
· age

| 

· home server

| 

· name  
  
· gender

| 

· domain name

| 

· mailing address  
  
· income level

| 

· E-mail address

| 

· telephone number  
  
| 

· site traffic

| 

· password  

4anything.com gathers most of the personal information it collects on its Users during an initial registration process for certain services such as E-mail or newsletters. Although some of the personal identifying information is necessary for 4anything.com to deliver certain of its services, most of the information collected is optional with respect to use of the 4anything.com Network. Accordingly, Users can determine to a large extent what information they wish to submit on a voluntary basis to 4anything.com.

In addition to the initial registration process, 4anything.com occasionally asks Users for personal information at other times, including when they complete optional survey forms or fill out optional contact forms for additional information on particular products and services.

**"Cookies"** "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser software on your computer's hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. The use of cookies is now an industry standard, and Users will find them on most major Websites. 

4anything.com sometimes uses cookies to store and track User information. Cookies enable 4anything.com to personalize the viewing experience of a User on the 4anything.com Network. When the User revisits the 4anything.com Network, 4anything.com can recognize the User by the cookie and customize the User's experience at the 4anything.com Network accordingly. For example, 4anything.com uses cookies to recognize User access privileges to the 4anything.com Network, track Site usage and traffic patterns, add advertisements for goods or services of interest, and estimate the 4anything.com Network's audience size. 

Although most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, if you prefer, a User may decline the placement of a cookie on his or her hard drive by using the appropriate feature(s) of one's web browser software (if available) to delete the cookie. Users should understand, however, that certain areas within the 4anything.com Network may not function properly if the web browser will not accept cookies.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Does 4anything.com disclose personal information to third parties?** 4anything.com discloses publicly available or volunteered technical or reference information of Users in aggregate form only, and not specific individual data, to advertisers and certain other third parties. For example, 4anything.com might tell an advertiser how many males between 20 and 30 years in age visited the 4anything.com Network during a particular period of time. 

In addition, Users are required to disclose certain personal information through registration in order to participate in promotions or to request information or a quote from certain third party providers that offer services through the 4anything.com Network (including requesting an insurance agent's or contractor's quote or information from a travel agent). It is necessary for 4anything.com to share this information with one or more appropriate third parties, who may or may not further transfer the information to appropriate vendors, in order to enable the vendors to provide the requested information or quote to the User. 4anything.com does not control these third parties, and there can be no assurance that certain of such parties will not solicit users in the future by E-mail or otherwise. If you do not wish to have your personal data shared with third parties, you may elect not to participate in promotions or use services that require the disclosure of personal data.

Except as stated above, 4anything.com does not disclose or transfer individual personal data records to third parties, unless it reasonably believes it is required to do so by applicable law or valid legal process or to protect its property interests.

4anything.com deals only with third party advertisers, retailers or service providers offering for sale products or services that 4anything.com believes may be of interest to Users of the 4anything.com Network. Nevertheless, 4anything.com is not and cannot be responsible for the activities or privacy policies of these third parties.

**What about external web sites?** To the extent that Users click on hyperlinks or banner advertisements to access third party sites from the 4anything.com Network, Users should understand that these third party sites may collect personally identifiable information about them. Users should further be aware that these third party Websites are not controlled by 4anything.com and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. Users should check the privacy policies of these third party Websites to see how their personal information will be utilized by the proprietors of these sites.

**What does 4anything.com do to keep the 4anything Network secure?** 4anything.com has also implemented a number of security features throughout the 4anything.com Network to prevent the unauthorized release of or access to personal information. For example, database information is kept separate from live servers and is firewall protected. Also, only authorized personnel have access to any stored personal information 4anything.com may collect on its Users. 

Please be advised, however, that although 4anything.com has endeavored to create a secure and reliable Site for its Users, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to/from 4anything.com via the 4anything.com Network or E-mail cannot be guaranteed. When disclosing any personal information, all Users should remain mindful of the fact that it is potentially accessible to the public, and consequently, can be collected and used by others without User consent. Accordingly, Users should consider carefully if they want to submit sensitive information that they would not want disclosed to the public and should recognize that their use of the Internet and the 4anything.com Network is solely at their own risk. 4anything.com has no responsibility or liability for the security of personal information transmitted via the Internet. 4anything.com, however, urges all of its Users to exercise caution when conveying personal information over the Internet.

**Can I opt-out of 4anything.com's data collection and/or distribution?** As noted earlier, the collection, use, and distribution of personal data greatly assist 4anything.com in creating a more, personalized, relevant, and intelligent service. Without the use of personal data, 4anything.com could not deliver certain of its content and services in the most beneficial way. Consequently, 4anything.com does ask for the submission of some personal data.

4anything.com does, however, offer Users of the 4anything.com Network the ability to "opt-out" of having their data collected or used as described in this Privacy Policy. Registration and the provision of any personal information is generally voluntary, unless necessary to provide certain services, such as E-mail. In addition, in the event that a User wishes to opt-out of 4anything.com's personal data use and collection practices after having submitted personal information, The User may send an E-mail to 

[4anything-request@news.4anything.com](mailto:4anything-request@news.4anything.com) to express his or her desire to opt-out. After receipt and processing of the User's opt-out E-mail, 4anything will refrain from further distributing the User's personal information to third parties that would otherwise be permissible under this Privacy Policy but for the opt-out. 4anything is not responsible for the use by third parties of personal information distributed to them prior to the User opting-out. 

**What about the collection of personal information from children?** 4anything.com does not intentionally collect or maintain information through its 4anything.com Network from individuals actually known to be under the age of 13 ("children"). Moreover, at present, no part of the 4anything.com Network is designed specifically to target or attract any children.

**Further Questions?** 4anything.com welcomes questions or comments Users may have regarding this Privacy Policy or the use of your personal data. Please send any questions or comments to 4anything.com to 

[ContactUs@4anything.com](mailto:contactus@4anything.com).

Your experience is extremely important to us.
